a leg lower ongc has also come off a
little bit it's down about half a
percent or so a little more than half a
percent i mean that's a full one one and
a half percent turn from the day's high
for ongc uh the uh intraday will come up
on your screen and i think you'll be
able to see that ongc is reacting now a
little more forcefully i think down
almost a full one percent or so so this
is uh what is uh coming through at this
stage as i said we'll have timzy join us
in just a bit to take us through some of
this in the meanwhile i don't know if
he'll have amburish with us
amrish if you've been listening in would
you want to react to the story which we
are putting out
on the oil and gas sector this time it's
gas and changing how often petrol and
diesel prices are revised go on
no i mean
as far as the your
revision of prices is concerned not on a
daily basis or fortnightly or monthly
basis
i don't think it will make any
difference at all i mean i mean we have
had couple of months when the prices did
not change because of the elections
and in the recent past also we have seen
that the prices don't change daily
because i mean all of us know it is
controlled remotely and it is not free
pricing but then if it becomes
possibly fortnightly or monthly i
suppose informed the customers can
possibly benefit because for example if
like
crude has moved sharply in uh like in
the last one month then possibly people
may fill up their tank just before the
increase which you i'm actually going to
do it uh if it was actually on a daily
basis this you can possibly do it uh if
it's fortnightly or monthly
yeah i mean look at owen gc by the way
that is i think it's a bit of a double
whammy now and if
apart from
crude gas is also included in that
so then it is two and a half percent
lower on ongc and uh you know
this is always going to be a bit of a
risk factor with some of these psu oil
marketing space to come you know
upstream and downstream both the kind of
companies
uh amrit good afternoon uh so
any any stock idea that you would have
looked at lately
uh yeah in fact today's recommendation
is in the general insurance sector ics
and lombard in fact the sector itself
has done quite
badly in the last two years because of
covet but now i'm expecting the general
insurance
premium to grow at about 12 percent for
the industry overall over the next
decade which is extremely good and uh in
fact uh isis lombard has today become
the largest in the private sector space
especially after the merger with the
bharti axa
and
i mean going ahead uh like this growth
will actually come from the strong
revival in the auto sector post covered
we have seen increased focus on health
insurance and now with the atomic
activity again showing a decent bounce
back commercial segment of general
insurance also uh should really see a
good bounce
and we have seen consolidation happening
in the sector the
strong ones are actually getting
stronger the number of players are
actually down from about 36 to 31 in the
last two three years and we have seen
psu players are actually losing market
share
so if you're uh i mean
looking at lombard then the net earned
premium over the next three to four
years i in fact i'm seeing 21 percent
cargo against uh 12 percent for the
industrial world this will be growing
much faster than the industry and we
should see the bat growth at about 30
percent cargo for the next three to four
years and in fact i have taken the risk
of recommending this talk today when the
earnings should be announced anytime
because i am in fact looking at the
longer term
again looking at q1 i'm expecting a 30
growth in the gross written premium it
should go to about 550 crores and net
premium should increase by about 21
percent looking at a path of 386 but in
case it disappoints i think it's an
option to buy at lower levels because
i'm looking at a target of
1575 uh because looking at an eps of
about 45 for fi 24 my target is 15.75
i'm just staying on we have more
questions for you for now we need to
take a break and we'll come back with
the market closing
you